[SPEAKER_01]: Nope, I wouldn't say so.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I mean, close in the sense that it's still within the vicinity of the greater Kuala Lumpur area, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Or what we would call the Kuala Lumpur Valley.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I think it would take at least like 30 to 40 minutes drive by car to get there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, most places I can get to within like 40 minutes by car in KL.
[SPEAKER_01]: Driving, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: So when you're in KL, when you go to other places, you mostly drive instead of taking public transport?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, although when I went to school, I took the train a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it was still developing, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: So like when I was in what we call secondary school, we had the, we had an LRT.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not sure why this stands for a light rapid, light rail transit.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so I would take that to school every day just because the traffic was really bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, but still the station would be like a 20 minute 15 to 20 minute drive from my place.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: So like, actually, if you wake up earlier, um, and you drive all the way to like all the way downtown, it's.
[SPEAKER_01]: faster.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just that the traffic was really bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's why we ended up doing public transport.
[SPEAKER_01]: But when I was 18, I think we had the new MRT.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so that kind of changed things.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I think transportation is getting better, but it's still a very predominantly car dependent society.